<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Contents on Project Not Cool</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Contents on Project Not Cool</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Part III</title>
      <link>/posts/part_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/part_3/</guid>
      <description>There was no way of knowing whose version would finally be adopted Once again he glanced at his rival in the opposite cubicle. Something seemed to tell him with certainty that Tillotson was busy on the same job as himself. There was no way of knowing whose version would finally be adopted, but he felt a profound conviction that it would be his own
Mare torrentur Mare torrentur tenuerunt Iovemque crudelis erat non manuque nullaque Pyreneus, evocet pectus, nube.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Part II : Retailers and More</title>
      <link>/posts/part_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/part_2/</guid>
      <description>Introduction One natural thought when comes to the factors contributing to youth tobacco issue would be like this: students of schools in the areas with more tobacco retailers must have easier accesses to the cigarettes, hence are more likely to be tempted. But are the high schools in the boroughs with higher retailer rate really closer to the retailers? We are trying to analysis the geographical pattern of high schools and registered tobacco retailers in this part.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Part I</title>
      <link>/posts/part_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/part_1/</guid>
      <description>He moved over to the window Since about that time, war had been literally continuous, though strictly speaking it had not always been the same war. For several months during his childhood there had been confused street fighting in London itself, some of which he remembered vividly.
Inside the flat a fruity voice was reading out a list of figures which had something to do with the production of pig iron.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
